My name is Nneamaka Edeh.
We come from Enugu State (Nigeria).
These are my siblings.
My parents died in 2005 and since then,
my sisters and I have been suffering for the past 5 years.
We have heard from the sister who said she is from Enugu State.
She said five years ago, their parents died and they have been orphans,
and she and the sister standing beside her have been the ones taking care of the siblings.
For the past five years since the death of their parents, they have been suffering.
Please, children of God, help us.
Who is caring for the house?
Just my sister and I.
My sister and I are sales girls in Enugu.
Are you not going to school?
I finished my secondary school
but my sister dropped out of secondary school while in SS1 after my parent's death.
This one is suffering from a shortage of blood
but there is no money to take her to hospital.
So what would you do to help them?
They are five in number. They should give each of them N100,000.
Put it in an account.
Please, people of God, come together and help.
Thank you, Man of God.
May God continue to bless you.
I am very grateful, thank you.
Ukamaka Edeh - Enugu, Nigeria
My name is Ukamaka Edeh. I am from Enugu State.
These are my other sisters. For the past five years since our parents died,
we have been struggling to feed our younger ones.
I dropped out of secondary school in SS1.
So, we came down from Enugu State where I am a sales girl.
But now, I am happy for what the man of God has done for us,
for giving us hope.
We are their family, they can come home here; this is their home.
We want to know how they are doing.
The one that is sick will be prayed for.
Those who want to go to school, people of God, please support.
Thank you.
So, they should immediately join the scholarship scheme.
We will give scholarships to these children
and let them go back to school. Thank you.
STANDARD FOR LIFE
My name is Nneamaka Edeh. I am 22 years old.
These are my siblings. We are orphans from Enugu State, Nigeria.
We are members of the Catholic church.
The problem that brought us to The SCOAN
was that our parents have been late since 2005.
There is no money, nobody cares.
For those five years, I have been working as a sales girl.
This is my younger sister who dropped out of school.
For five years we have been suffering
because there is nobody to help us.
Things are rough, even to eat and to pay our house rent...
The worst is that my younger sister sitting there is sick with shortage of blood
but there is no money to take her to the hospital.
Yesterday, we came to The SCOAN by night bus.
Even when my parents were alive, I never saw this amount of money.
The man of God gave us N500,000, five bags of rice
and scholarships to any level we want to go to.
I am so happy; I don't know what to say.
I am short of words.
I thank God.
Since morning, I have been saying to myself, "Is this me and can God do this for me?"
I am so happy. I thank God and give Him the glory.
Before - I can't lie, this is in the presence of God -
at times, I slept with men because of money.
But I promised God that if He helps me and my family, all that rubbish will stop.
I will never go back to my past life. I really thank God for my life.
This is a great miracle which I never expected in my life.
My name is Ukamaka Edeh. Nneamaka is my elder sister.
I am the second born.
We are from Enugu State, Nigeria. For the past five years that our parents died,
we have been struggling to take care of our younger ones.
I am a sales girl like my sister.
Pastor T.B. Joshua gave us N500,000 and five bags of rice.
He also gave me and my younger ones scholarships
so that we can go back to school.
I am very grateful. May God bless T.B. Joshua.
My name is Edeh Chinyere.
I am very grateful because before, there was nothing to eat,
let alone go to school.
God has really answered our prayers because when we came here,
we received a cash gift of N500,000 and five bags of rice.
I am very grateful. May God bless T.B. Joshua.
My name is Miracle.
How do you feel today seeing the man of God blessing you with such huge amount of money -
N500,000 - five bags of rice, a copy of the Holy Bible, and this wonderful book?
I feel very happy.
My name is Chinedu.
I am sick.
I am short of blood.
My sisters don't have money to take care of me.
Now that you have come to a place where
Jesus Christ had paid the price for your healing,
and through the grace in the life of His anointed servant,
you are set free from your illness
and you have also been blessed by the anointed man of God
with N500,000, a copy of the Holy Bible, the Mirror book, and five bags of rice.
How do you feel?
I feel very happy.
Glory be to God that you can have a cause to smile
in spite of the pains that you are going through.
And indeed, Jesus Christ is the answer to all fundamental issues of life.
I am so happy.
My advice to people out there - because I know there are many people like us.
All I can say to them is that they should have faith and be patient with God.
God's time is the best. When God blesses you and lifts you up,
that is the best for everyone.
I really thank God.
The hope you have been given today, is an everlasting one
because you have just found a father that is greater than all fathers
and a friend that is closer than a brother.
That is Jesus Christ in the life of His anointed servant Prophet T.B. Joshua.
And with what God Almighty has done in your lives,
we want to encourage you to stay in faith in Christ Jesus
and remember that it is for the salvation of your soul
that God Almighty has blessed you immensely.
And we want to pray that God will give you the inner grace
to live by the Word of God and this blessing you have received
will multiply in Jesus' name.
Amen.